Checkpoint 
15.1 What is a GUI? 
15.2 What is JavaFX? 
15.3 What is a component? 
15.4 What is an event? What is an event listener?
Checkpoint 
15.5 What is a scene graph? 
15.6 What are the three types of nodes in a scene graph? 
15.7 What type of scene graph node can have children? What type cannot?
Checkpoint
15.8 What is FXML? 
15.9 What type of file does Scene Builder save a GUI to? 
15.10 Which Scene Builder panel provides a list of JavaFX components? 
15.11 Which Scene Builder panel do you use to visually design an application’s GUI? 
15.12 Which Scene Builder panel shows the scene graph? 
15.13 Which Scene Builder panel allows you to work with a component’s properties, 
 layout, and code? 
15.14 What is an fx:id?
Checkpoint 
15.15 In general, what operations does the main application class perform? 
15.16 What is the controller class? 
15.17 What is an event listener? 
15.18 How do you register a controller class to an application’s GUI in Scene Builder? 
15.19 How do you register an event listener to a component in Scene Builder?
Checkpoint 
15.20 You want the user to be able to select only one item from a group of items. Which type of component would you use for the items, RadioButtons or CheckBoxes? 
15.21 You want the user to be able to select any number of items from a group of items. Which type of component would you use for the items, RadioButtons or CheckBoxes? 
15.22 What is the purpose of a toggle group? 
15.23 Do you normally add RadioButtons or CheckBoxes to a toggle group?
Checkpoint 
15.24 What ImageView property do you set in the Inspector panel to display an image? 
15.25 What method do you call to change an ImageView’s image?

econ new notes: dissave (taking money out of your saves)